Teng-Yuan Liu (Shuk)

<u>biz.shuk@gmail.com</u>, +886- 911-839-712 <u>GitHub, http://shuk.info/</u>, TOEIC 655

Summary

Full-Stack engineer, Strong learning ability and motivation. Adaptable and responsible. Love to assist colleagues's tech problems and challenges.

Experience in back-end service, web application, game development,

Experience in user behavior analysis, integration, automation, DevOps (docker, kubernets).

Familiar with e-commerce, marketing concept

Work Experience

Full-Stack Engineer | FreeCodeCamp

09/2015 -

Online javascript and back-end certification

Half of trainings now, Has abilities for Full-Stack, just go through for the Certification.

Cloud Engineer | Shanghai Droi Tech Ltd. | Taipei, TW

07/2015 -

Internet company, 500+ people, from device hardware to PaaS

- Nginx (Openresty) customize configuration with Lua, include auto-compile Lua to Luac and activate Luajit.
- Lua profiler for checking lua script syntax and block some dangerous system call api.
- Model lua commit flow and Integrate with CI tools (Ansible and Jenkins).

Game and BI developer | Gamesofa Inc. | Taipei, TW

11/2012 - 04/2015

Online Game company, 200 people, self-made games including Mahjong, Poker, FPS, and RPG

- Use HTML5, CSS, js to develop Win8 App "Godgame big two", integrate billing service, connect with backend server, adjust lobby UI.
- Develop server side of "Godgame Texas Hold'em" for event and features e.g. different kind of friend list, server API [PHP, Perl, HTML, CSS, js]
- Implement Omaha server rule [Perl]
- [Marketing group] Develop survey system and deploy to different location server solve global location latency issue ,and custom advanced options for avoiding ui or ordered sequential option making useless data.
- [Marketing group] Develop user analyzing system which is showing user retention rate, payment and activated situations with user(pm) defined group, and easy to use for product manager and online marketing specialist.
- [Marketing group] Analyze user behavior and do A/B testing with data analyst.
- [Marketing group] Refactor custom service system, deleting useless code and merge code files.

Alternative civilian service | Dept. of Civil Servant Development | Taipei, TW

12/2011 - 11/2012

Government unit, 50 people, for training gov staff

• Assist staff to discuss system spec of <u>Taipei e-campus</u>, suggest and negotiate with 3th-party engineers.

Web developer | National Central University | Jongli, Taiwan

03/2010 - 06/2011

College of Taiwan, 5th rank

Setup websites, bypass library system for ebook search, saving \$20000 at least and maintaining fee

Other Experience

• Housekeeper | Motel 6 W&H (working holiday) | Moab, UT 06/2011 - 11/2011 US Working Holiday project(J1 visa). Co-work with American, Mexican, Indian, Russian, China, and Turks.

Code Skills and tools

• Code Skill: PHP, Perl, Nodejs, RESTful concept, MVC concept, Single Page App concept, bash

HTML5, CSS (SASS, bootstrap, pure, RWD), javascript (React.js, AngularJS 1.x, jQuery)

• Server Apache, Nginx, Mysql,

Development Docker, Trello, TravisCI, Github, Parse, kubernetes
OS: Linux(Ubuntu 14.04, main dev env), Windows, Mac

• Tools: Vim, Sublime, Skype, line

Education

- M.S. in CS, National Central University, Jongli, Taiwan, 2011, June.
- B.S. in CS, National Dong-Hua University, Hualien, Taiwan, 2009, Jan.